Guide to the Nancy Ottmann Albert Papers, 1981 - 2006
Nancy Ottmann Albert Papers1981 - 2006
- Series IV. Photographs
  - Binder 11: 5" x 7" research photos for New England Mill Project, 1981-1984 (Binder 1)
    - Cranston, RI, R-C-6 (Binder 1)
      3 photos
    - Exeter, RI, R-E-2 (Binder 1)
    - East Greenwich, RI, R-E-1 (Binder 1)
    - Forestdale, RI, R-F-2 (Binder 1)
    - Stone worker housing 1810-15, Fistreville, RI, R-F-1 (Binder 1)
    - Victorian cottage Georgiaville, RI, R-G-1 (Binder 1)
      1 photos
    - Harrisville, RI, R-H-3a (Binder 1)
      9 photos
    - Kenyon, RI, R-K-1 (Binder 1)
    - Lippitt Mill, Lippitt, RI, 1809, R-L-1 (Binder 1)
      4 photos
    - Lafayette Mill, North Kingston, RI, R-N-3a (Binder 1)
    - Hamilton Web Co., North Kingston, RI, R-N-3 (Binder 1)
      11 photos
    - Shady Lea Mill, North Kingston, RI, R-N-3b (Binder 1)
    - Atlantic Mill, Olneyville, RI (N. Providence), 1851, R-O-1 (Binder 1)
    - Unmarked photos of construction (Binder 1)
    - Sayles Mill, Pascoag, RI, R-P-1 (Binder 1)
    - Pawtucket, RI, R-P-2 (Binder 1)
      6 photos
    - Phenix, RI, R-P-3 (Binder 1)
    - Providence, RI, R-P-5 (Binder 1)
    - Peacedale Mills (Kingston), R-P-6, Aug '82 (Binder 1)
    - Royal Mill, Riverpoint, RI, R-R-1 (Binder 1)
    - Rockville, RI mills R-R-2 (Binder 1)
    - Rodman Mill, South Kingston, RI R-S-3b (Binder 1)
    - Slatersville, RI, R-S-1 (Binder 1)
    - Woonsockett, RI mills, R-W-1 (Binder 1)
      15 photos
    - White Rock Mill, Westerly, RI, R-W-2 (Binder 1)
    - West Warwick, RI mills, R-W-3 (Binder 1)
    - Westerly, RI mills, R-W-4 (Binder 1)
    - Pontiac Mill complex, Warwick, RI, R-W-5 (Binder 1)
      8 photos
  - Binder 10: 5"x7" research photos for New England Mill Project, 1981-1984 (Binder 1)
    - Home Woolen Mills, C-B-2 (Binder 1)
    - Quinebaug Co., Danielson, CT, C-D-1a (Binder 1)
    - Eliotville lower mill, East Killingly, CT, C-E-2b (Binder 1)
    - Unmarked photos (Binder 1)
    - East Hampton, CT, mill, C-E-1 (Binder 1)
    - Grosvenordale mills, C-G-1 (Binder 1)
    - North Grosvenordale mills, C-N-1 (Binder 1)
    - Williams Flannel Mill, Norwich, CT, C-N-3 (Binder 1)
    - Putnam, CT, mills, C-P-1 (Binder 1)
    - Restoration of a building in Cheney Bros complex, Manchester (Binder 1)
    - Rockville, CT mills, C-R-1 (Binder 1)
      16 photos
    - Taftville, CT mills, C-T-1 (Binder 1)
    - Unmarked photos (Binder 1)
    - Clerestory, Ponemah Mill, 1971, C-T-1 (Binder 1)
    - Tarriffville, CT mills, C-T-2 (Binder 1)
    - Uncasville, CT mills, C-V-1 (Binder 1)
      14 photos
    - Bertha raising the flag and water tower, American Thread (Binder 1)
    - Wauregan Mills 1853, Wauregan, CT, C-W-1 (Binder 1)
    - American Suspender Mill, Waterbury, 1843, C-W-5 (Binder 1)
    - Yantic Woolen Mill, Yantic, CT, C-Y-1a (Binder 1)
      7 photos
    - Chicopee, MA mills, M-C-1 (Binder 1)
    - East Douglas, MA mills, M-E-1 (Binder 1)
    - Fall River, MA mills, M-F-1 (Binder 1)
    - Millworkers on break, Fall River, MA, M-I-1a (Binder 1)
    - Gilbertville, MA, M-G-1 (Binder 1)
    - Tennements, Holyoke, MA, M-H-1 (Binder 1)
    - Merrick Thread Co., Aug '82, Main St. Building, Jan '82 (Binder 1)
    - Restored townhouses, Nov. 1983, re-used warehouse now banquet facility, Jan '82 (Binder 1)
    - Mill and commerical building, Holyoke (Binder 1)
    - Ornamental work on Merrick Thread Co., old building, Holyoke, MA (Binder 1)
    - Hinsdale, MA mill, M-H-2 (Binder 1)
    - Housatonic, MA mills, M-H-3 (Binder 1)
    - Manchuag, MA mills, M-M-1 (Binder 1)
    - Pontoosic Mill, Pittsfield, MA, M-P-1 (Binder 1)
    - Thorndike, MA, M-T-1 (Binder 1)
    - Whitinsville, MA mills, M-W-1 (Binder 1)
    - Linwood Mill and mill office, Witinsville, MA, M-W-2 (Binder 1)
    - Carolina, RI mill ruins (Binder 1)
    - Cheshire Mill, Harrisville, N. Hampshire (Binder 1)
    - Grocery, Hillsborough, New Hampshire (Binder 1)
    - Haromony Mills, Cohoes, New York (Binder 1)
    - Railroad station, Thomaston, CT, March '84 (Binder 1)
    - Commercial structures, Manyunk, PA, June '84 (Binder 1)
    - 17th centruy houses, Salem, MA, Aug '84 (Binder 1)
    - Houses south of England, Dec '70 (Binder 1)
    - Lake Compounce, Bristol, CT, Sept. '84 (Binder 1)
    - Ornate tower, downton Suncook, NH, Sept. '84 (Binder 1)
    - Apartment balcony and tennement porch, Holyoke, MA, Feb '84 (Binder 1)
    - Church, Riverton, CT Dec. '82 (Binder 1)
    - Commercial buildings, Holyoke, MA, Sept '82 (Binder 1)
    - Church, Thomaston, CT, March '84 (Binder 1)
  - Box 4--New England, 1982-1986 (Binder 1)
    - North Grosvenordale, CT. Aug. 1981. The Beginning (Binder 1)
    - American Thread, Willimantic, CT, 1981-1983 (Binder 1)
    - Northampton, MA, 1982 (Binder 1)
    - Harrisville, RI, 1982 (Binder 1)
    - Fall River, MA, Aug. 1982 (Binder 1)
    - Newmarket, NH, Aug. 1982 (Binder 1)
    - Dover, NH, Aug. 1982 (Binder 1)
    - Hillsborough, NH, c. 1982 (Binder 1)
    - Whitsinsville, MA, 1982 (Binder 1)
    - Pawtucket RI area, c. 1982-3 (Binder 1)
    - Unknown mill window, c. 1983 (Binder 1)
    - Oxoboxo River, CT, Jan. 1983 (Binder 1)
    - North Grosvenorsdale, CT. February, 1983, Sept. 1995, Sept. 1996 (Binder 1)
    - Chicopee, MA, 1983 (Binder 1)
    - Merrick Thread, Holyoke, MA, 1982 (Binder 1)
    - Holyoke, MA, c. 1983, March 1995 (Binder 1)
    - Saxony Mill, Rockville, CT. c. 1983 (Binder 1)
    - Carolina, RI, c. 1983 (Binder 1)
    - Pontiac Mills, Cranston, RI, Nov. 1983 (Binder 1)
    - Rockville, PA. June 1984 (Binder 1)
    - Pontcosic Mill, Putnam, CT, June 1984 (Binder 1)
    - Salem, MA. Aug. 1984 (Binder 1)
    - Lake Compounce, Bristol, CT, Sept. 1984 (Binder 1)
    - Beacon Falls, CT. June 1988 (Binder 1)
    - Mt. Desert Island, ME, 1988 (Binder 1)
    - Willimantic, CT, April 1989 (Binder 1)
    - Pittsfield, MA, Sept. 1990 (Binder 1)
    - Saratoga NY area, Oct. 1990 (Binder 1)
    - Bellows Falls, VT Aug. 1991-Oct. 1992 (Binder 1)
    - Rte. 20, NY State, Aug. 1991 (Binder 1)
    - Feeding Hills, MA, 1991-1992 (Binder 1)
    - Windsor, CT 1991 (Binder 1)
    - Suffield, CT 1991 (Binder 1)
    - Westfield, MA, Nov. 1991-Mar.1992 (Binder 1)
    - Southampton, MA, Mar. 1992 (Binder 1)
    - Maple Syrup + Honey House, Blandford area, MA, 1991 (Binder 1)
    - Deep River, CT 1992 (Binder 1)
    - RI October 1992 (Binder 1)
    - Uxbridge, MA area. Jan. 1993, Sept. 1996 (Binder 1)
    - North Plains, CT, July-September 1993, Nancy Smith pump (Binder 1)
    - Wadsworth Mansion, Middletown, CT, July 1993 (Binder 1)
    - Shad Shack, Sept. 1993 (Binder 1)
    - Hartford, CT, September-October 1993 (Binder 1)
    - Worcester, MA, railroad Sept. 1993 (Binder 1)
    - Middletown, CT, Sept. 1993, Dec. 1995 (Binder 1)
    - Portland, CT, Nov. 1993 (Binder 1)
    - abandoned couch, Mystic, CT, Nov. 1993 (Binder 1)
    - Durham, CT, April 1994 (Binder 1)
    - South Glastonbury, CT, July 1994 (Binder 1)
    - Harkness Greenhouse, Watertown, CT, July 1994 (Binder 1)
    - New Dawn Dairy, Lyme area, Nov. 1994 (Binder 1)
    - Lyme area, CT, Feb. 1995 (Binder 1)
    - Southeastern, CT, July 3, 1995 (Binder 1)
    - Baltic Mill, Baltic, CT, July 1995 (Binder 1)
    - Rockville, RI, July 1995 (Binder 1)
    - Rte. 1, Maine, July 1995 (Binder 1)
    - House near Rte. 2, Orange, MA 1995 (Binder 1)
    - Bernardston, VT area, Oct. 1995 (Binder 1)
    - Portland, CT Jan. 1995 (Binder 1)
    - Bernardston, MA Oct. 1995 (Binder 1)
    - Slaterville, MA, Sept. 1996 (Binder 1)
    - Rhode Island Blackstone River area, Nov. 1996 (Binder 1)
  - Box 5--Mill towns mostly, 1998-1999 (Binder 1)
    - North Lonsdale, RI June 1998 (Binder 1)
    - South Lonsdale, RI June 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Lonsdale, RI June 1998 (Binder 1)
    - West Warwick, RI, June 1998 (Binder 1)
      18 photos
    - Griswold Airport, CT June 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Watch Hill RI, June 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Dartmouth area, NH July 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Hanover NH area, July 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Lisbon area, NH July 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Church interior, Cheever, NH July 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Hillsborough, NH July 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Harrisville, NH July 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Lonsdale Village, RI June 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Cheaver NH, July 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Quanset Point, RI July 1998 (Binder 1)
    - E. Greenwich area, RI, July 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Shannock, RI July 1998 (Binder 1)
      13 photos
    - Westerly RI, July 1998 (Binder 1)
    - North Adams, MA Aug. 1998/9 (Binder 1)
      38 photos
    - Providence, RI Aug. 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Woonsockett, RI Aug 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Valley Falls, RI Aug. 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Warwick RI, Pontiac Mills Aug. 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Holyoke, MA Sept. 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Northampton, MA Sept. 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Easthampton, MA Sept. 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Taftville, CT Ponomeh Mill Oct. 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Baltic Mill, CT Oct. 1998, Aug. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Hartford CT, Oct.-Oct. 1999 (Binder 1)
      23 photos
    - Thomaston, CT April 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Migrant worker camp, Southwick, MA April-June 1999 (Binder 1)
      photos
    - Collins Axe Co., Collinsville, CT June 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Thorndike, MA June 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Indian Orchard, MA June 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Belchertown, MA June 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Collinsville, CT June 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Torrington, CT June 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Middletown, CT Nov. 1998 (Binder 1)
    - American Thread, Willimantic, CT Aug. 15, 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Groton, CT Aug. 1999 (Binder 1)
      12 photos
    - Western, MA Aug. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - North Adams area, August 1999 (Binder 1)
    - new Canaan, CT Aug. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - East Windsor, CT Aept. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - South Windsor, CT Sept. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - South Glastonbury, CT Sept. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Rte. 17 Glastonbury, CT Sept. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Crittenfen Mfg. Middletown, CT Oct. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Hatfield, MA Oct. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Fitchburg, MA Oct. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Newmarket, NH area Oct. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Hubbardston, MA Oct. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Lawrence, MA Oct. 1999 (Binder 1)
  - Box 6--New England, 2000-2005 (Binder 1)
    - Lille area, ME June 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Potato barn, St. John River Valley, ME June 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Madawashra area, ME, June 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Field of toilets, Winchendan, MA July 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Rocky Hill, CT, July 2000 (Binder 1)
    - West Granville/Granville, MA, July 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Brooklyn, NY August 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Enfield, NH Oct. 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Franklin, NH Oct. 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Middlefield, CT Nov. 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Bushnell Park, Hartford, CT Feb. 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Wilde Building, CIGNA, Bloomfield, CT, April 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Maitland, NS June 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Along Rte. 1, ME, June 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Frog bridge, Willimantic, CT June 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Chelsea, VT July 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Brattleboro, VT July 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Pontiac Mills, Warwick, RI, Oct. 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Baltic, CT, Nov. 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Haddam, CT, Jan. 2002 (Binder 1)
    - New London, CT, Jan. 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Webster Theater, Hartford, CT, Dec. 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Ware, MA June 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Winchendon, MA June 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Berwick, ME June 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Topsham, ME June 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Bucksport, ME June 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Granby, CT Aug. 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Rte. 5, MA, Sept. 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Along Rte. 156, Haddam, CT, April 2003 (Binder 1)
    - St. Augustine, FL, Jan. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Claremont, NH, area, March 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Bellows Falls, NH March 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Les Ils de la Madelaine, Canada, June 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Souris area, PEI June 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Magdalen Islands, Quebec June 2003 (Binder 1)
    - PEI fishing shacks, June 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Along Rte. 1, ME June 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Hudson Valley, NY July 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Boston, MA "Big Dig", Aug. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Suffield, CT Oct. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - St. Johnsbury, VT Nov. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Keene, NH Nov. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Old Saybrook, CT Jan. 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Holyoke, MA March 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Old Lyme, CT April 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Middletown, CT April 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Along Connecticut River near Portland, 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Ocean House, Watch Hill, RI, April 2004 (Binder 1)
    - West Mystic, CT May 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Manchester, NH May 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Grosse Ile, Quebec July 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Along Rte. 7, VT July 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Harkness Memorial greenhouse, Waterford, CT, Aug. 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Brattleboro, VT area Feb. 2005 (Binder 1)
    - Norwich, CT area, April 2005 (Binder 1)
    - Paupers Home southeast of Grantham, NH July 2005 and Grantham area (Binder 1)
  - Box 7--Institutions, includes state hospitals, Belchertown, Long River Village, Long Lane School, 1998-2005 (Binder 1)
    - Northampton State Hospital, MA, Sept. 1998 (Binder 1)
      17 photos
    - Norwich State Hospital CT, Oct. 1998 (Binder 1)
      27 photos
    - Farfield State Hospital, Newton, CT, May 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Belchertown State School and Hospital, MA, June 1999 (Binder 1)
      20 photos
    - Mansfield Training Center--CT, June 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Howard Center, Cranston, RI Oct. 2001 (Binder 1)
    - CT Valley Hospital, Middletown, CT, Jan 1994-Nov. 1999 (Binder 1)
      32 photos
    - Long River Village, Middletown, CT, June-Dec. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Long Lane School, Middletown, CT, Nov. 2001-June 2005 (Binder 1)
      33 photos
    - Wesleyan University Long Lane campus map (Binder 1)
    - Unmarked B+W photo of young girl raking (Binder 1)
    - 5 photos of brick building (Binder 1)
    - "The End of the Village" reception postcard (Binder 1)
  - Box 8--Abroad 1991-2000, includes France 1991, 1992, 1994, 1996, Portugal, Spain, London, Italy (Binder 1)
    - Brittany (France), June 1991 (Binder 1)
    - Carnac, France, June 1991 (Binder 1)
    - Chartres, France June 1991 (Binder 1)
    - Paris June 1991-March 1996 (Binder 1)
      268 photos
    - Les Gras, France July 1992 (Binder 1)
    - Orleans, France May 1994 (Binder 1)
    - Bourges, France May 1994 (Binder 1)
    - Arles, France May 1994 (Binder 1)
    - France 1994 (Binder 1)
    - St. Gilles, France May 1994 (Binder 1)
    - Abbaye at Nantes, France March 1996 (Binder 1)
    - Sainte, France, March 1996 (Binder 1)
    - Perigaux, France March 1996 (Binder 1)
    - L'Abbaye Fonteuraud France, March 1996 (Binder 1)
    - France, Languedou area, March 1996 (Binder 1)
    - Lisbon, Alfama area March 1997 (Binder 1)
    - Evora, Portugal March 1997 (Binder 1)
    - Obidas, Portugal March 1997 (Binder 1)
    - Marvao, Portugal, March 1997 (Binder 1)
    - Bourgos Cathedral, Spain March 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Guggenheim Museum, Bilbac, Spain, March 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Segovia, Spain March 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Avila, Spain March 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Spain, March 1998 (Binder 1)
    - kew gardens, London May 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Greenwich, UK May 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Royal Naval Hospital, May 1999 (Binder 1)
    - London May 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Greenwich Observatory, UK May 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Montapulchiano, Italy March 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Tuscany, Italy March 2000 (Binder 1)
    - San Gimmiano, Italy March 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Piltigano, Italy March 2000 (Binder 1)
    - San Galgano Abbey, Italy March 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Siena, Italy March 2000 (Binder 1)
    - St. Rocco a Pilli, Italy March 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Volterra, Italy March 2000 (Binder 1)
    - Venice, Italy March 2000 (Binder 1)
      21 photos
  - Box 9--Abroad 2001-2008, includes: Cuba, Eastern Europe, Vienna, Barcelona, Bosnia, Slovenia, Croatia, Berlin (Binder 1)
    - Havana, Cuba March 2001 (Binder 1)
      66 photos
    - Cojimar, Cuba, March 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Unmarked photo of ornate doorway (Binder 1)
    - Prauge July 2002 (Binder 1)
      28 photos
    - Nurenberg, Germany July 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Along the Danube, July 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Regensburg, Germany July 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Passau, Germany July 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Haas Maus, Vienna July 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Karlsplatz Station, Vienna, July 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Kanlskirke, Vienna July 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Gallerie-Vienna July 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Budapest Market, July 2002 (Binder 1)
    - Vative Kirke, Vienna Oct. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Palm Haus, Vienna, Oct. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Belvedere Palace, Vienna Oct. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Vienna, Oct. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Risenrad, Prater-Vienna Oct. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Gasometers, Vienna Oct. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Otto Wagner Station, Vienna Oct. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Shoenbrunn Palace, Vienna Oct. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Heitzig, Austria Oct. 2003 (Binder 1)
    - Barcelona Nov. 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Casa Milla, Barcelona Nov. 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Parc de la Ciudad, Barcelona Nov. 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Parc de Pedrables, Barcelona Nov. 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Gaudi Gate, Barcelona Nov. 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Monestir, Barcelona Nov. 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Parc Guell, Barcelona Nov. 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Opatia, Croatia March 2008 (Binder 1)
    - Pula, Croatia March 2008 (Binder 1)
    - Berlin--March 2008 (Binder 1)
  - Box 10--Assorted mounted 8"x11"s from several shows
    - Durham, CT April 1994
    - Diner, Middletown, CT April 1994
      1 photo
    - Glastonbury, CT July 994
    - Main Street, Holyoke, MA March 1995
    - North Grosvenordale, CT Sept. 1995
    - Cabins along the Mohawk Trail, MA Oct. 1995
    - Rhode Island, July 1998
    - Rhode Island Millpond (Shannock), July 1998
    - Baltic Mill, CT (since burned) Oct. 1998
    - Hartford, CT Oct. 1998
    - Railroad station, Thomaston, CT April 1999
    - Fairfield Hills State Hospital, Newtown, CT May 1999
    - South Brittain, CT May 1999
    - Havana, Cuba March 2000
    - Higganum, CT 2000
    - Rocky Hill, CT July 2000
    - Along Rte. 1, Maine June 2001
    - Budapest Market, July 2002
    - Vienna, Oct. 2003
    - Haas Haus Vienna, 2003
    - Middletown, CT August 2004
    - Little Sugar Creek, Dec. 2010
  - Box 11--11"x14"s all years, mounted Long River Village 8"x10"s
    - Bellows Falls, VT Aug. 1991
    - West Warwick, RI June 1998
    - Royal Mill, West Warwick, RI, June 1998
    - Lonsdale Drive-In, S. Lonsdale, RI, June 1998
    - Northampton State Hospital, MA Sept. 1998
    - Norwich State Hospital (CT), Oct. 1998
    - Connecticut Valley Hospital, Middletown, CT, Nov. 1999
    - Hartford, CT Oct. 1998
    - International Barber Shop, Hartford, CT Oct. 1998
    - Center for the Arts, Wesleyan University, Middletown, CT 1998
    - Middletown, CT, view from Arigoni Bridge, Nov. 1998
    - Thomaston, CT Railroad Station, April 1999
    - Thomaston, CT April 1999
    - North Adams, MA Aug. 1999
    - Baltic Mill after fire, Baltic, CT, August 1999
    - Groton area, CT August 1999
    - Long River Village, Middletown, CT, prior to demolition 1999
      9 11"x14" photos; 11 mounted 8"x10" photos
    - Havana, Cuba March 2000
    - Spain, 1998
    - Franklin, NH Oct. 2000
    - Howard Center, RI (Cranston), Oct. 2001
    - Winchendon, MA June 2002
    - St. Augustine, FL Jan. 2003
    - Magdalen Islands, Canada June 2003
    - Fishing Shacks, Prince Edward Island, June 2003
    - Old Saybrook area, CT Jan. 2004
    - Hanover area, NH March 2004
    - Gillespie's Gas, Rowan County, WC April 2006
    - Campcall Store, NC (Shelby Area) March 2006
    - Granville, MA
    - "Portrait of Havanna" exhibition labels (Binder 1)
      5 items
  - Box 12--Mounted 8"x10"s 1984-1993, Holyoke, Westfield, CT vernacular
    - Holyoke, MA 1984
    - Abandoned car, Missouri 1985
    - Suffield, CT 1989
    - Pre-restoration Wadsworth Mansion, Middletown, CT 1990
    - Photo Deep River, CT, Feb. 1991
    - Honey House, Agawam, MA (Feeding Hills) 1991
    - Bellows Falls, VT Aug. 1991
    - Old Saybrook, CT Oct. 1991
    - Westfield, MA March 1992
    - Mill pond, Slateville, RI Jan. 1993
    - Hartford, CT 1993
    - Windsor, CT 1993
    - Granby, CT May 1993
    - Nancy Smith's pump 1993
    - Nancy Smith's silo, North Plains, CT Sept. 1993
    - North Plains, CT Sept. 1993
    - Haddam, CT Nov. 1993
    - Old Charter Oak Bridge, Hartford Oct. 1993
    - Middletown, CT c. 1994
  - Box 13--France 1992-96, mostly Paris, matted 8"x10"s
    - Paris 1994
    - Paris 1996
    - Orleans, France 1996
    - Paris 1992
    - France 1996
    - Les Gras, France 1992
    - Perigaux, France 1996
  - Box 14--France mostly Paris, 1991, includes some in glass (1992-94)
    - Paris 1991
      4 photo
    - Carnac, France 1991
      2 photo
    - Cemetery in a small French Village, 1992
    - Paris 1992
      6 photo
    - Paris 1994
  - Box 15--Good but not exhibition quality prints, 1999-2005 (Binder 1)
    Note: many photos are not labeled with location or date
    - Howard Center, RI Oct. 2001 (Binder 1)
    - New Hampshire, July 2001 (Binder 1)
    - Western MA, Aug. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - View from Arrigonia Bridge, Middletown CT, Nov. 1998 (Binder 1)
    - Chataqua, June 1993 (Binder 1)
    - San Diego, CA Nov, 1992 (Binder 1)
    - Southampton, MA March 1992 (Binder 1)
    - West Mystic, CT May 2004 (Binder 1)
    - Majestic Theater, Easthampton, MA (Binder 1)
    - Collinsville, CT June 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Lawrence, MA Oct. 1999 (Binder 1)
    - Norwalk Hall, Fairfield (Binder 1)
    - Unlabled Photos (Binder 1)
      236 photos